

# **AIRLANGGA** YUDIATAMA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

## CONTACT



Whatsapp

+62 812 8481 7372



mail

airlangga.yudiatama@outlook.com

## **ABOUT ME**

Hello, my name is Airlangga you can call me "air" or "angga". I'm a Software Engineer and I can be a Fullstack Developer too.

I have been years in programming I specialize focused in Backend Python or Java, I care deeply about build Microservice and Integration.

### **SOCIAL MEDIA**



Github

github.com/airgg



LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/airlangga-yudiatama



Website

airgg.netlify.app

### **EDUCATION**

### **JAKARTA STATE POLYTECHNIC**

INFORMATICS ENGINEERING: 2020 - 2024

### **CCIT - FACULTY OF ENGINEERING UNIVERSITY OF INDONESIA**

COMPUTER SCIENCE: 2020 - 2022

### **SMKN 1 CIBINONG**

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING: 2017 - 2020

# **LANGUAGES**

## **ENGLISH**

CONVERSATIONAL

### **INDONESIAN**

**FLUENT** 

# **AWARDS**

#### 2023

- National Polytechnic Informatics Student Competition: KMIPN (Finalist Hackathon).
- Web Developer Competency Professional Certification (LSP Jakarta State Polytechnic).

## 2022

- Programmer Competency Professional Certification (LSP University of Indonesia)
- Student Creativity Program: PKM (Finalist Pass Funding).
- National Polytechnic Informatics Student Competition: KMIPN (Finalist Best Poster).

### **SKILLS**

**PYTHON** 



**JAVASCRIPT** 



**JAVA** 

**FLUTTER** 

# MISC

CORELDRAW



**PHOTOSHOP** 



**FIGMA** 

# #

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **FREELANCE**

SINCE JUN 2019 - PRESENT

### **INTERNSHIP**

PT ELANG MAHKOTA TEKNOLOGI TBK. | AUG - DEC 2023

# AIRLANGGA YUDIATAMA

airlangga.yudiatama@outlook.com | +6281284817372 | linkedin.com/airlangga-yudiatama github.com/airgg | airgg.github.io | Bogor, Jawa Barat, Indonesia

# **Educations** \_

- 1. Jakarta State Polythechnic (Bachelor Degree). GPA 3.5. Informatics Engineering. 2020 2024.
- 2. CCIT Faculty of Engineering, University of Indonesia (Associate Degree). GPA 3.64. Computer Science. 2020 2022.
- 3. SMKN 1 Cibinong (Vocational High School). GPA 3.0. Software Engineering. 2017 2020.

# Experience

### PT Elang Mahkota Teknologi Tbk.

Internship Fullstack Developer. Aug 2023 - Dec 2023

- Developed a website to monitor the status of IoT (Internet of Things) devices integration with sensor for doing remote procedure call. This website for monitoring and visualization data telemetri from sensor IoT.
- Tools: Python, FastApi, NuxtJS, VueJS, PostgreSQL (Web)

### **Depok City Health Department**

Project Based Learning - Community Service. May 2023 - Sep 2023

- Developed the simkesling website, this website is for hospital and puskesmas waste management and data collection of transporters who transport the waste as a report.
- Tools: PHP, Laravel, NextJS, ReactJS, MySQL (Web)

#### PT Fedora Cakra Informatika

Freelance Android Developer. Mar 2023 - Apr 2023

- Developed Apps with login multi user. This apps is for create queue and check queue, see doctor's schedule, room information, emergency call and see the location of the hospital and deployed for three hospital in Makassar, Sumatera and West Java.
- Tools: Dart, Flutter, Rest API (Android)

### PT Bank Pembiayaan Rakyat Syariah Dinar Ashri

Freelance Fullstack Developer. Nov 2022 - Mar 2022

- Developed Web E-Collateral with login multi user, multi level and deployed in multi branch company. This web is for management inventory and location collateral of bank customer.
- Tools: Python, FastApi, VueJS, PostgreSQL (Web)

#### **Depok City Health Department**

Project Based Learning - Community Service. Jul 2022 - Aug 2022

- Developed Web Lalapan Depok with login multi user and multi level. This web for Online Food Safe Training Class, so the food handlers and drinking water depots in the city of Depok can get a certificate Food Sanitation Hygiene (HSP).
- Tools: PHP, Laravel, MySQL (Web)

### Bank Pembangunan Daerah: BPD Yogyakarta

Freelance Fullstack Developer. Jun 2022 - Jul 2022

- Develope Web for Rekonsal and Reversal Transaction PPOB. This web is like tools for supporting main PPOB Banking Application BPD Yogya.
- Tools: Python, FastApi, VueJS, SQLite (Web)

#### Koperasi Usaha Putera Pribumi: KUPP

Freelance Fullstack Developer. Dec 2021 - Feb 2022

- Developed Web Tracking Taxi Airport Soekarno-Hatta with multi login user and multi level. This web for manage driver, car, transaction integration with Google Maps and Firebase for Realtime detect driver and report.
- Developed Apps Tracking Taxi Airport with login multi user. This apps for driver to get order, for the driver states ready and Realtime tracking where the driver is.
- Tools: Python, FastApi, VueJS, SQLite, Firebase (Web) | Flutter, SQLite, Firebase (Android)

### Kementerian Kelautan dan Perikanan: KKP

Freelance Fullstack Developer. Sep 2021 - Dec 2021

- Developed Web E-Commerce Training video for Trainer with login multi user and multi level. This web for manage video, selling video training, print receipt, report.
- Developed Apps Lautku with login multi user and multi level. This apps for trainer upload new video and user for buying video and view video.
- Tools: Python, Flask, VueJS, MySQL (Web) | Flutter, MySQL, SQLite (Android)

### **Overpast Experience**

Freelance Fullstack Developer. Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

I have 3 other industry experience with more than 1 year. Stacks: Java, Spring, Python, Flask, Javascript, VueJS, SQLServer, MySQL.

# Competition / Certificates \_

All available certificates: https://bit.ly/airgg18-certs

### 2023

- National Polytechnic Informatics Student Competition: KMIPN (Finalist Hackathon).
- Programmer Competency Professional Certification (LSP Jakarta State Polytechnic).

### 2022

- Programmer Competency Professional Certification (LSP University of Indonesia).
- Student Creativity Program: PKM (Finalist Pass Funding).
- National Polytechnic Informatics Student Competition: KMIPN (Finalist Best Poster).

### 2020

Software Development KKNI Level 2 Competency Professional Certification (LSP SMKN1 Cibinong).

#### 2010

• 6th/180+ Zoom Educare Program (Finalist Grade of Excellent).

#### 2018

1st Place Skills Competition Bogor (LKS).

# Misc

- Start Learning Programming in first year vocational high school.
- Design entushiast.
- Fast self-taught, Highly adaptive, Interest to learn something new.
- Love Badminton and Traveling